export const chapter = "Chapter - 10: Adverb";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "What is an Adverb primarily responsible for in a sentence?",
          optionA: "Modifying nouns",
          optionB: "Modifying verbs, adjectives, or other adverbs",
          optionC: "Establishing conjunctions",
          correctAnswer: "b) Modifying verbs, adjectives, or other adverbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of an Adverb of Manner?",
          optionA: "Tomorrow",
          optionB: "Quickly",
          optionC: "Always",
          correctAnswer: "b) Quickly",
        },
        {
          question: "What do Adverbs of Time indicate in a sentence?",
          optionA: "Manner of an action",
          optionB: "Place of an action",
          optionC: "Time when an action is done",
          correctAnswer: "c) Time when an action is done",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where should Adverbs of Degree be placed in a sentence according to the general rules?",
          optionA: "At the beginning",
          optionB: "In the middle",
          optionC: "At the end",
          correctAnswer: "b) In the middle",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the function of Interrogative Adverbs?",
          optionA: "Expressing doubt",
          optionB: "Asking questions",
          optionC: "Indicating certainty",
          correctAnswer: "b) Asking questions",
        },
        {
          question: "Which type of Adverb refers back to its antecedent?",
          optionA: "Relative Adverbs",
          optionB: "Adverbs of Place",
          optionC: "Adverbs of Time",
          correctAnswer: "a) Relative Adverbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In what position should Adverbs showing place or direction be placed in a sentence?",
          optionA: "At the beginning",
          optionB: "In the middle",
          optionC: "At the end",
          correctAnswer: "c) At the end",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When an Adverb modifies a Transitive Verb, where should it be placed?",
          optionA: "Between the Verb and its Direct Object",
          optionB: "Before the Verb",
          optionC: "After the Verb",
          correctAnswer: "a) Between the Verb and its Direct Object",
        },
        {
          question: "Which Adverb is always used after the word it modifies?",
          optionA: "Only",
          optionB: "Never",
          optionC: "Enough",
          correctAnswer: "c) Enough",
        },
        {
          question: "What type of Adverbs can be used to compare?",
          optionA: "Adverbs of Place",
          optionB: "Adverbs of Time",
          optionC: "Adverbs of Manner, Adverbs of Time, and Adverbs of Degree",
          correctAnswer:
            "c) Adverbs of Manner, Adverbs of Time, and Adverbs of Degree",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "An Adverb is a word that adds to the meaning of an Adjective, a Verb, or another Adverb in a sentence. Adverbs can modify ________________ in a sentence.",
          optionA: "Nouns",
          optionB: "Verbs",
          optionC: "Adjectives",
          correctAnswer: "b) Verbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Manner show the manner in which an action is done. For instance, 'The officer shouted at the clerk angrily.' What is the Adverb of Manner in this sentence?",
          optionA: "Highly",
          optionB: "Merrily",
          optionC: "Angrily",
          correctAnswer: "c) Angrily",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Time indicate the time when an action is done. In the sentence 'We play cricket daily,' what type of Adverb is 'daily'?",
          optionA: "Adverb of Manner",
          optionB: "Adverb of Time",
          optionC: "Adverb of Place",
          correctAnswer: "b) Adverb of Time",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs showing place or direction are placed in the ___________.",
          optionA: "Beginning",
          optionB: "Middle",
          optionC: "End",
          correctAnswer: "c) End",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Degree show the quantity or extent of an action. Identify the Adverb of Degree in the sentence 'The job was completely done.'",
          optionA: "Completely",
          optionB: "Done",
          optionC: "Job",
          correctAnswer: "a) Completely",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is an Interrogative Adverb?",
          optionA: "Daily",
          optionB: "How",
          optionC: "Never",
          correctAnswer: "b) How",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The boy was sliding the staircase downwards,' where should the Adverb showing place or direction be placed?",
          optionA: "Beginning",
          optionB: "Middle",
          optionC: "End",
          correctAnswer: "c) End",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When an Adverb modifies a Transitive Verb, it should not be placed between the Verb and its ___________.",
          optionA: "Subject",
          optionB: "Object",
          optionC: "Adjective",
          correctAnswer: "b) Object",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of definite frequency are generally placed in ______________.",
          optionA: "Beginning",
          optionB: "Middle",
          optionC: "End",
          correctAnswer: "c) End",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The rabbit was walking slower than the turtle,' what type of Adverb is 'slower'?",
          optionA: "Adverb of Manner",
          optionB: "Adverb of Time",
          optionC: "Adverb of Degree",
          correctAnswer: "c) Adverb of Degree",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3)
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs modify nouns, verbs, or other adverbs in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of Manner show the time when an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of Time indicate the time when an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Degree show the quantity or extent of an action.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Interrogative Adverbs are used to make statements rather than ask questions.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Relative Adverbs refer back to their antecedents.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs showing place or direction are always placed at the beginning of a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs modifying Transitive Verbs should be placed between the Verb and its Direct Object.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Enough is always placed before the word it modifies.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs can only be used to compare Adjectives, not other Adverbs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };

export var activityData;
